

# CONTACT

- 09356436243
- ✓ r.salmani.programming@gmail.com
- Markazi, Arak

# **EDUCATION**

2014 - 2016

**BENAB UNIVERSITY** 

• Master of Physices

## **SKILLS**

- Senior FrontEnd
- Public Relations
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

## **TALENTS**

- Javascript
- Angular
- React
- Vue
- SonarQube
- Testing (jest, cypress)
- Google LightHouse
- Docke
- Client-GraphQl RestFull api
- Css (Tailwind, sass,scss,css)
- UI (material,prime,....)

# LANGUAGES

- Persian (Fluent)
- English (Intermediate)

# **REZA** SALMANI

# SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

I am Reza Salmani. My real journey began in 2019 when I applied for a frontend job at Pardazesh Argham Yansa Corp. I worked there for six months before relocating to Arak, where I joined ArisRayaneh Corp in 2020. I continue to work there today as a Senior Frontend Developer.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Aris Rayaneh Novin

Senior Frontend Developer

2020 - PRESENT

 Develop and execute frontend projects, such as ERPs, startups, and more...

#### Pardazesh Argham Yasna

Junior Frontend Developer

2019- 2020

 Develop and execute frontend projects, such as ERPs, commercial websites, startups, and more...

### **Asre Maharat Institute**

Teaching Front-End development

2024 - PRESENT